<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grocery Stories</title>
    <link>http://grocerystories.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Grocery Stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 10:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://grocerystories.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Beetroot Cake</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/chocolate-beetroot-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/chocolate-beetroot-cake/</guid>
      <description>While at university in 2012, my friend Daniella and I started a blog called Shitty Photos of OK Food. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot that makes me smile on there, but it&amp;rsquo;s the documented experience of cooking regularly and sometimes competitively with a great friend that I&amp;rsquo;m especially glad to have.
Chocolate beetroot cake really caught my attention that year, and has done ever since. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, let me tell you: chocolate and beets combined are delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Garden</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/paradise-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 21:49:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/paradise-garden/</guid>
      <description>Hakan Aktaş’s smile and the fruit and vegetables he picks up five nights a week from New Spitalfields Market are what keep people shopping at his greengrocers, Paradise Garden. There’s a Tesco Express and Sainsbury’s Local across the street, and yet Paradise Garden persists and has done so for six years now.
Hakan comes from Karahasanuşağı Köyü, a predominantly Kurdish community in Elbistan, Turkey. A river cuts through the eastern side of Karahasanuşağı Köyü, a valley town with a small forest and some agricultural land and mountains in the distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 17:10:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Sarah Eden. Grocery Stories is about community and food. It started out mostly about grocery stores — places I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested ever since shopping and working at a family-run Lebanese grocery store as a teenager — but then it grew because getting the ingredients is only the middle.
You&amp;rsquo;ll find stories here about the people, shops, and food I love most, around London and in places I visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Grocery Story</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/a-grocery-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 21:32:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/a-grocery-story/</guid>
      <description>Grocery stores began to pique my interest as a teenager when the local shop of my youth, Barbur Foods in SW Portland, Oregon, changed hands and the aisles transformed. I remember going into the store as a kid, hand in my dad’s big hand, for a pack of Winston cigarettes, a box of Cheerios, and a stop in front of their two “foreign food” shelves to pick up Jacob’s crackers or Keiller’s marmalade, products my dad missed from home.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>