<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Places on Grocery Stories</title>
    <link>http://grocerystories.net/categories/places/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Places on Grocery Stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 21:49:49 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://grocerystories.net/categories/places/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Garden</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/paradise-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 21:49:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/paradise-garden/</guid>
      <description>Hakan Aktaş’s smile and the fruit and vegetables he picks up five nights a week from New Spitalfields Market are what keep people shopping at his greengrocers, Paradise Garden. There’s a Tesco Express and Sainsbury’s Local across the street, and yet Paradise Garden persists and has done so for six years now.
Hakan comes from Karahasanuşağı Köyü, a predominantly Kurdish community in Elbistan, Turkey. A river cuts through the eastern side of Karahasanuşağı Köyü, a valley town with a small forest and some agricultural land and mountains in the distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newington Green Fruit and Veg</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/newington-green-fruit-and-veg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/newington-green-fruit-and-veg/</guid>
      <description>If you find a finer selection of local and global produce in North London, let me know. I&amp;rsquo;ve found white asparagus, golden kiwis, purple yams, green almonds, and red gooseberries in Newington Green — and that&amp;rsquo;s only the produce with colours in their names. The shop is always bustling, thus the turnover is high and the fruit and veg you come home with is always fresh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar snap, please</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/sugar-snap-peas-with-mustard-seeds-and-tarragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 22:43:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/sugar-snap-peas-with-mustard-seeds-and-tarragon/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Saturday in May. Find yourself in Portland, Oregon at the PSU Farmers Market. Stop by Groundwork Organics&amp;rsquo;s stall and, casting aside the umbrella you thought would be necessary for visiting this city, buy as many sugar snap peas as you can carry. Pick a tree to lean on and crack open the peas, delight at the snapping and occasional pea popping, and eat the pods whole.
A time may come when you feel like eating something other than sugar snap peas alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puntarelle and co </title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/puntarelle-and-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/puntarelle-and-co/</guid>
      <description>Two to three times a month I walk, tube, walk, run (through a pigeon-filled tunnel), and walk to Puntarelle &amp;amp; Co (formally John &amp;amp; Elena Fruit &amp;amp; Veg). This takes me, round trip, about 2.5 hours, but I&amp;rsquo;m not complaining. For rarely more than a tenner, I come away with some of the best British and Italian produce you can buy in London.
Puntarelle &amp;amp; Co is open to the public on Saturdays, from early morning to around 2pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yildiz</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/yildiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/yildiz/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d never seen a store like Yildiz until I moved to London. You pass by piles of flat peaches, pomegranates, crook cucumbers, and cantaloupes — and before you know it you find yourself pulled into the the shop and surrounded by mountains of grains, dozens of types of halva, and fresh olives, cheese, nuts, and bread. On the topic of bread, a lot of Yildiz&amp;rsquo;s comes from their bakery next door, a bakery where you can get the finest gözleme in London for £2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Grocery Story</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/a-grocery-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 21:32:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/a-grocery-story/</guid>
      <description>Grocery stores began to pique my interest as a teenager when the local shop of my youth, Barbur Foods in SW Portland, Oregon, changed hands and the aisles transformed. I remember going into the store as a kid, hand in my dad’s big hand, for a pack of Winston cigarettes, a box of Cheerios, and a stop in front of their two “foreign food” shelves to pick up Jacob’s crackers or Keiller’s marmalade, products my dad missed from home.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>