<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Grocery Stories</title>
    <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Grocery Stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 08:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://grocerystories.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch babies</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/dutch-babies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/dutch-babies/</guid>
      <description>January and February are hard months for me, and probably for some of you too. My father died last May. This fact has been making difficult experiences I&amp;rsquo;d normally find easy and making harder those which I&amp;rsquo;d have found hard at any point in my life.
So, it&amp;rsquo;s a time of sadness and here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m doing all the same:
 walking and generally exercising as much as I can; talking to people I love; thinking about all I have to be grateful for; and making what feels good to eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Camisa</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/i-camisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 10:32:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/i-camisa/</guid>
      <description>When Cristina Onuta first entered I Camisa &amp;amp; Son in 1999, the shop still had sawdust on the floors — to prevent people from slipping after rain — and cured sausages dangling from the ceiling. While regulations have put an end to these trademarks, little else about the shop has changed since it opened in Soho in 1961.
At age 20, Cristina Onuta left Romania to take a six-month English course in London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate beetroot cake</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/chocolate-beetroot-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/chocolate-beetroot-cake/</guid>
      <description>While at university in 2012, my friend Daniella and I started a blog called Shitty Photos of OK Food. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot that makes me smile on there, but it&amp;rsquo;s the documented experience of cooking regularly and sometimes competitively with a great friend that I&amp;rsquo;m especially glad to have.
Chocolate beetroot cake really caught my attention that year, and has done ever since. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, let me tell you: chocolate and beets combined are delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise Garden</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/paradise-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 21:49:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/paradise-garden/</guid>
      <description>Hakan Aktaş’s smile and the fruit and vegetables he picks up five nights a week from New Spitalfields Market are what keep people shopping at his greengrocers, Paradise Garden. There’s a Tesco Express and Sainsbury’s Local across the street, and yet Paradise Garden persists and has done so for six years now.
Hakan comes from Karahasanuşağı Köyü, a predominantly Kurdish community in Elbistan, Turkey. A river cuts through the eastern side of Karahasanuşağı Köyü, a valley town with a small forest and some agricultural land and mountains in the distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newington Green Fruit and Veg</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/newington-green-fruit-and-veg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/newington-green-fruit-and-veg/</guid>
      <description>If you find a finer selection of local and global produce in North London, let me know. I&amp;rsquo;ve found white asparagus, golden kiwis, purple yams, green almonds, and red gooseberries in Newington Green — and that&amp;rsquo;s only the produce with colours in their names. The shop is always bustling, thus the turnover is high and the fruit and veg you come home with is always fresh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar snap, please</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/sugar-snap-peas-with-mustard-seeds-and-tarragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 22:43:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/sugar-snap-peas-with-mustard-seeds-and-tarragon/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Saturday in May. Find yourself in Portland, Oregon at the PSU Farmers Market. Stop by Groundwork Organics&amp;rsquo;s stall and, casting aside the umbrella you thought would be necessary for visiting this city, buy as many sugar snap peas as you can carry. Pick a tree to lean on and crack open the peas, delight at the snapping and occasional pea popping, and eat the pods whole.
A time may come when you feel like eating something other than sugar snap peas alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e5 bakehouse bread making class</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/e5-bakehouse-bread-making-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/e5-bakehouse-bread-making-class/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve talked about how e5 bakehouse&amp;rsquo;s bread making class took me over the final hurdle to making great sourdough bread at home. Check out their website for the latest dates on their beginner and advanced classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puntarelle and co </title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/puntarelle-and-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/puntarelle-and-co/</guid>
      <description>Two to three times a month I walk, tube, walk, run (through a pigeon-filled tunnel), and walk to Puntarelle &amp;amp; Co (formally John &amp;amp; Elena Fruit &amp;amp; Veg). This takes me, round trip, about 2.5 hours, but I&amp;rsquo;m not complaining. For rarely more than a tenner, I come away with some of the best British and Italian produce you can buy in London.
Puntarelle &amp;amp; Co is open to the public on Saturdays, from early morning to around 2pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking bread</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/breaking-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 15:18:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/breaking-bread/</guid>
      <description>I watched a TV show as a kid that featured a monk happily making bread, folding and kneading away in his black robe, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a quest to make good bread myself ever since. That quest involved a lot of reading and failed attempts at home before I finally sought the help of professionals.
With a lot of classes I&amp;rsquo;ve tried, I managed to make an OK loaf on the day, but then failed when trying to follow the whole process at home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasticcini di mandorle</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/pasticcini-di-mandorle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 18:57:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/pasticcini-di-mandorle/</guid>
      <description>I like to make notes in my cookbooks to remind myself of what went right and wrong with the recipe. Lower heat next time. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget the baking powder! Even better the day after. After I&amp;rsquo;ve made a recipe a number of times or generally feel I&amp;rsquo;ve got the hang of it, I just put a tick beside the title. My pages of Rachel Roddy&amp;rsquo;s Five Quarters: Recipes and Notes from A Kitchen in Rome are full of tick marks and pasticcini di mandorle — soft almond biscuits — has six of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yildiz</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/yildiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/yildiz/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d never seen a store like Yildiz until I moved to London. You pass by piles of flat peaches, pomegranates, crook cucumbers, and cantaloupes — and before you know it you find yourself pulled into the the shop and surrounded by mountains of grains, dozens of types of halva, and fresh olives, cheese, nuts, and bread. On the topic of bread, a lot of Yildiz&amp;rsquo;s comes from their bakery next door, a bakery where you can get the finest gözleme in London for £2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Alice pizzeria masterclass</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/radio-alice-pizzeria-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 08:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/radio-alice-pizzeria-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve had Radio Alice pizza (or pizza from their sister pizzerias in Italy at Berberè), you&amp;rsquo;ll already have asked yourself the question, &amp;lsquo;how do they make it so good?&amp;rsquo; Learn the answer to this question, enjoy pizza and wine on the day, and take home a starter to practice at home &amp;ndash; all for a steal at £15. Find out when their next masterclass is on here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A grocery story</title>
      <link>http://grocerystories.net/posts/a-grocery-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 21:32:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://grocerystories.net/posts/a-grocery-story/</guid>
      <description>Grocery stores began to pique my interest as a teenager when the local shop of my youth, Barbur Foods in SW Portland, Oregon, changed hands and the aisles transformed. I remember going into the store as a kid, hand in my dad’s big hand, for a pack of Winston cigarettes, a box of Cheerios, and a stop in front of their two “foreign food” shelves to pick up Jacob’s crackers or Keiller’s marmalade, products my dad missed from home.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>